A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 FA1410
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Project Files, 1982-2015; 1
  - The Network, Inc. and Human Media - "Barely Getting By" Humankind #126/127 Answering the Needs (Parts 1 and 2), 2008 (Box 37, Folder 230)
    Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction
  - New Brunswick Theological Seminary - Administration Reorganization, 2004-2012 (Box 38, Folder 231-233)
  - New York City Public/Private Initiatives - Comprehensive Assessment of the City University of New York (CUNY), 1998-1999 (Box 38, Folder 234)
  - New York Regional Association of Grantmakers (NYRAG) (Philanthropy New York) - Membership Dues, 2004-2009 (Box 38, Folder 235-236)
  - New York Theological Seminary - Center for World Christianity, 2005-2013 (Box 39, Folder 237-238)
  - New York Theological Seminary - Intergenerational Korean Clergy, 2000-2004 (Box 39, Folder 239-240)
  - New York Theological Seminary - Master of Professional Studies Program, Sing Sing (Box 39, Folder 239-240)
  - Northern Illinois University - Cambodian American Heritage Museum, 2005-2009 (Box 39, Folder 241-242)
  - Northland College - Superior Connections, 2006-2012 (Box 40, Folder 243-244)
  - Oberlin College - International Perspective in Environmental Studies, 2002-2011 (Box 40, Folder 245)
  - Oberlin Shansi - Centennial Book, 2005-2008 (Box 66, Folder 417)
  - Oberlin Shansi - Renewing the Commitment to Joining Worlds (Box 66, Folder 417)
  - Oberlin Shansi Memorial Association, 1985-1989 (Box 40, Folder 246)
  - Ocean Conservancy - Ocean Wilderness: Crown Jewels of the Sea, 2001-2003 (Box 40, Folder 247)
  - Georgia O'Keeffe Museum - Georgia O'Keeffe and Ansel Adams: Natural Affinities, 2007-2009 (Box 40, Folder 248)
  - Albert G. Oliver Program, 1985-1988 (Box 40, Folder 249)
  - Orion Society - Environmental Studies Book Award, 2007-2012 (Box 41, Folder 250)
  - Pacific Institute - National Assessment of the Water Resources of the United States: A Sustainable Vision, 2006-2012 (Box 41, Folder 251)
  - Pacific School of Religion - Asian American and Pacific Islander Religious Leaders, 2005-2013 (Box 67, Folder 418-421)
  - Pacific School of Religion - Institute for Leadership Development, 1999-2003 (Box 41, Folder 252)
  - Parrish Art Museum - Augustus-Saint Gaudens, American Sculptor, 2003 (Box 41, Folder 253)
  - Partners for Livable Places, 1985-1988 (Box 41, Folder 254)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - Training Academy for Congregational Partnerships and Resources, 2002-2005 (Box 41, Folder 255-256)
  - Partners for Sacred Places - New Dollars, New Partners for Your Sacred Places (Powerpoint Presentation) (Box 41, Folder 255-256)
  - Peking University - Luce Pavilion Restoration, 1985-1990 (Box 42, Folder 257)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - American Art Center, 2003-2006 (Box 42, Folder 258)
  - Philadelphia Museum of Art - James Castle: Hear Me with Your Eyes, 2007-2009 (Box 42, Folder 259)
  - Pittsburgh Theological Seminary - History of World Christian Movement, 1999-2012 (Box 42, Folder 260-261)
  - Plymouth Congregational Church - Round Table Connections, 2001-2009 (Box 67, Folder 422-423)
  - Potomac Associates, 1984-1994 (Box 42, Folder 262)
  - Princeton-In-Asia - Summer Chinese Language Program, 1992-2003 (Box 43, Folder 263)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - China Missions Guide, 1985-1988 (Box 43, Folder 264)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - Dutch Theology Rare Book Collection, 1999-2000 (Box 43, Folder 265)
  - Princeton Theological Seminary - 50th Anniversary Award, Asian Ministry, 1986-1992 (Box 43, Folder 266)
  - Private Sector Council, 1986-1989 (Box 43, Folder 267)
  - Public Radio International - Asia, 2006-2009 (Box 43, Folder 268)
  - Public Radio International - Asia Coverage, 2005 September (Box 43, Folder 268)
  - Purdue University - Religion in China, 2003-2007 (Box 68, Folder 424-425)
  - Resources for the Future, 1984-1990 (Box 43, Folder 269-270)
  - Rocky Mountain Institute - Transforming the Electric Utility Industry, 2004-2012 (Box 68, Folder 426)
  - Rubin Museum of Art - Bon: The Magic World (Religious Tradition of Tibet and the Himalayas), 2007-2008 (Box 44, Folder 271-272)
  - St. Ann Chapel, 1997-2003 (Box 44, Folder 273-276)
  - St. John's College (Santa Fe, New Mexico), 1984-1991 (Box 44, Folder 277)
  - St. Johns University - Theology and the Arts, 2001-2013 (Box 68, Folder 427-429)
  - St. Johns University - The Saint John's Bible (Box 68, Folder 427-429)
  - St. John's University - Four Loves, Frank Burch Brown, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 427-429)
  - St. Joseph of Arimathea Foundation, 2002-2005 (Box 45, Folder 278)
    Material related to St. Ann Chapel.
  - St. Louis Art Museum - Art of the Osage, 2003-2004 (Box 45, Folder 279)
  - St. Louis Art Museum - George Caleb Bingham, 1986-1991 (Box 45, Folder 280)
  - San Francisco Theological Seminary - Southern California Program, 2000-2012 (Box 45, Folder 281-282)
  - Seminario Evangelico de Puerto Rico - Technology and Faculty Development, 2001-2012 (Box 45, Folder 283-284)
  - Settlement College Readiness Program, 1985-1988 (Box 46, Folder 285)
  - Singapore Institute of International Affairs - SIAA Internships, 2005-2013 (Box 69, Folder 430)
  - Skidmore College - Object Exhibition and Knowledge, 2008-2009 (Box 69, Folder 431)
  - Social Science Research Council - Christianity Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 286)
  - Social Science Research Council - Committee on Southeast Asia, 1986-1991 (Box 46, Folder 287)
  - Social Science Research Council - Indochina Studies, 1986-2011 (Box 46, Folder 288)
  - Society of Biblical Literature - International Meeting, Singapore, 2005-2013 (Box 69, Folder 432)
  - Sojourners - Coverage of Religion and the Arts, 1999-2003 (Box 46, Folder 289-290)
  - Sound Portraits Productions - StoryCorps Oral History Project, 2004-2007 (Box 69, Folder 433-434)
  - Sound Portraits Productions - Danny and Annie Perasa StoryCorps Broadcast on NPR's Morning Edition and Listener Response, 2006 (Box 69, Folder 433-434)
  - Sound Portraits Productions - StoryCorps Sampler, Hosted by Dave Isay, 2003 (Box 69, Folder 433-434)
    1. Welcome, Reggie Jones
    2. June and LeAlan Jones
    3. Sandy Birnbaum
    4. Bernie Halperin
    5. The Teitelbaums
    6. Willaim Feehan
    7. Mary Lou Lollis
    8. Joe Caracciolo
    9. Clyde "Kingfish" Smith
  - Sound Portraits Productions - StoryCorps Sampler, Volume 2, Hosted by Dave Isay, 2005 (Box 69, Folder 433-434)
    1. Welcome Danny and Annie Perasa
    2. Philomena Luciani
    3. Kaitlyn Sever and Lynne Lande
    4. Harold Slappy and Monia Esteban
    5. Debbie Fisher
    6. Kim and Amy Schumer
    7. Billy Collins and Nancy Cobb
    8. Michael Wolmetz and Debora Brakarz
  - Stanford University - Chinese Scholar Xu Chengshi, 1986-1988 (Box 46, Folder 291)
  - Stanford University - Inter University Program (IUP), 1986-1992 (Box 46, Folder 292)
  - State University of New York at Albany - Nelson A. Rockefeller Institute of Government, 1986-1992 (Box 46, Folder 293)
  - Staten Island Botanical Garden - Programming and Staffing, 2001-2013 (Box 69, Folder 435)
  - Statue of Liberty - Ellis Island Foundation, 1986-1987 (Box 47, Folder 294)
  - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1984-1987 (Box 47, Folder 295)
  - Summit School - Campaign for Kids, 2002 (Box 47, Folder 296)
  - Syracuse University - Delegation Visit to North Korea, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 297)
  - Tanenbaum Center for Interreligious Understanding - Building Blocks for Democracy Program, 2000-2004 (Box 47, Folder 298)
  - Tate Gallery - Edward Hopper, 2003-2005 (Box 69, Folder 436-437)
  - Textile Museum - Hippie Chic Exhibit, 2007-2009 (Box 47, Folder 299)
  - Tides Center - Beijing China Project (Center for Digital TV and the World), 2008-2009 (Box 47, Folder 300)
  - Tricycle, 2001-2002 (Box 47, Folder 301)
  - Trilateral Commission - East Asia and the International System Study Group, 1999-2002 (Box 70, Folder 438)
  - Tricycle Foundation - Development Program, 2003-2005 (Box 47, Folder 302-303)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists - Sound Science Solutions to Global Warming, 2001-2012 (Box 48, Folder 304-305)
  - Union Theological Seminary, 1984-1993 (Box 48, Folder 306-307)
  - Union Theological Seminary - Encyclopedia of Women and Religion in North America, 1999-2012 (Box 48, Folder 308)
  - Union Theological Seminary - Henry Luce III Chair in Reformation History, 2000-2012 (Box 70, Folder 439-440)
  - Union Theological Seminary - A Union of Spirit: An Interactive Video Tour of Union Theological Seminary in the City of New York (Box 70, Folder 439-440)
  - Union Theological Seminary - Presbyterian School of Christian Education (Union Presbyterian Seminary), 2003-2012 (Box 49, Folder 309-310)
    Grant support for the Institute of Reformed Technology.
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Central Philippine University, 1986-1991 (Box 49, Folder 311)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Nalini Jayasuriya, 1986 (Box 49, Folder 312)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Payap University Chapel, 1982-1989 (Box 49, Folder 313)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Yale Divinity School, 1986-1989 (Box 49, Folder 314)
  - United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia - Yonsei Chapel, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 315)
  - United States Fund for UNICEF - Southeast Asia Tsunami Relief Efforts, 2005 (Box 70, Folder 441)
  - United States Indonesia Society - Higher Education Conference, Jarkarta, 2005-2012 (Box 70, Folder 442)
  - United States Indonesia Society - Partnership for Higher Education, 2005-2009 (Box 70, Folder 443)
  - United Theological Seminary of the Twin Cities - Society for Arts in Religious Theological Studies, 2003-2005 (Box 70, Folder 444)
  - Universidad Francisco Marroquin - Stillman Fund, 1986-1991 (Box 49, Folder 316)
  - University of California, Berkeley, 1984-1989 (Box 49, Folder 317)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Vietnamese Studies Journal, 2005-2009 (Box 50, Folder 318-319)
  - University of California, Los Angeles - Korean Christianity Program, 2004-2009 (Box 50, Folder 320)
  - University of California Press - American Art of the 18th and 19th Centuries: A Documentary Anthology, 2004-2009 (Box 50, Folder 321)
  - University of California, Riverside - Southeast Asian Library Collection, 2005-2012 (Box 50, Folder 322)
  - University of California, San Diego - Pacific Rim Digital Library Alliance, 1998-2012 (Box 50, Folder 323)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz - Interdisciplinary Training in Environmental Management, 2004-2013 (Box 70, Folder 445)
  - University of Chicago, Divinity School - Scholarship in Theology and Religion, 1999-2004 (Box 51, Folder 324-325)
  - University of Dayton - Theology Doctorate Program, 2003-2005 (Box 51, Folder 326)
  - University of Dubuque - Native American Commissioned Lay Pastors, 2004-2012 (Box 71, Folder 446-447)
  - University of Hong Kong, 1985-1990 (Box 51, Folder 327)
  - University of Kansas - History of Christianity in China, 1985-1987 (Box 51, Folder 328)
  - University of Michigan - SEASSI Institute, 1985-1988 (Box 51, Folder 329)
  - University of Puget Sound - Environmental Decision Making and Policy Initiative, 2002-2012 (Box 52, Folder 330)
  - University of Washington - Cambridge History of Korea, 1993-2008 (Box 71, Folder 448)
  - University of Washington - Traditional Contemporary Aboriginal Art for Taiwan, 2006-2007 (Box 71, Folder 449)
  - University of Washington - Vietnamese Advanced Summer Institute, 1995-2002 (Box 71, Folder 450)
  - University of Wisconsin, Madison - Southeast Asian Studies Summer Institute, 1994-2004 (Box 52, Folder 331-332)
  - Valparaiso University - "Seeing Was Believing" Illustrations, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 333)
  - Vanderbilt University - Divinity School, 1983-2005 (Box 53, Folder 334-336)
  - Vermont Law School - Environmental Law Clinic, 2003-2012 (Box 71, Folder 451)
  - Vero Beach Museum of Art - George Rickey: A Retrospective, 2005-2009 (Box 72, Folder 452-453)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum - Marsden Hartley, 2000-2003 (Box 53, Folder 337)
  - Wadsworth Atheneum - Wallace Nutting and the Invention of Old America, 2002-2007 (Box 72, Folder 454)
  - Wake Forest University - Divinity School Multi-disciplinary Courses, 1997-2002 (Box 54, Folder 338)
  - Wake Forest University - Expand Courses and Support for a Theological Librarian, 2003-2013 (Box 72, Folder 455)
  - Washington Theological Union - Formation for Ministry Program, 2003-2012 (Box 54, Folder 339)
  - Weatherspoon Art Gallery - American Art Collection Research (ACE) (University of North Carolina, Greensboro), 2000-2003 (Box 54, Folder 340)
  - Wellesley College - 50th Anniversary Award, 1986-1992 (Box 54, Folder 341)
  - Wesley Theological Seminary, 1994-1999 (Box 54, Folder 342)
  - Wesleyan University - Christian Colleges in the United States and China, 1999-2006 (Box 55, Folder 343)
  - West Virginia University Foundation - Jingdezhen Ceramics Institute Exchange Program, 2008-2010 (Box 55, Folder 344-345)
  - Whitney Museum of American Art - Buckminster Fuller: The Geometry of Thought, 2007-2008 (Box 55, Folder 346)
  - Wichita Art Museum - American Library Collection Digitization, 2006-2009 (Box 55, Folder 347-348)
  - Wildlife Conservation Society - Masoala National Park, 2000-2005 (Box 56, Folder 349)
  - Williams College Museum of Art - Moving Pictures: Early Film and American Realist Painting, 1895-1910, 1999-2005 (Box 56, Folder 350)
  - Winterthur Museum, Country Estate - Silversmiths to the Nation: Thomas Fletcher and Sidney Gardiner, 2005-2008 (Box 56, Folder 351)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution - Changing Attitudes, Advancing Women, 2001-2002 (Box 56, Folder 352)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution - Oceanographic Science and Public Policy, 2001-2005 (Box 56, Folder 353)
  - Woods Hole Research Center - Renewable Energy Model, 2001-2003 (Box 56, Folder 354)
  - Woodstock Theological Center - Catholicism and Civic Renewal, 2003-2013 (Box 73, Folder 456-458)
  - Woodstock Theological Center - Women and Theology Program, 2010-2013 (Box 73, Folder 459)
  - Woodstock Theological Center - Women and Leadership in the Church and the World, 2011-2012 (Box 73, Folder 460)
  - World Learning - New York Ambassadors Program, 2000-2004 (Box 57, Folder 355-356)
  - World Monuments Fund - Center for Khmer Studies, Cambodia, 2000-2004 (Box 57, Folder 357-358)
  - World Resources Institute - Global Forest Watch, 2000-2004 (Box 57, Folder 359-360)
  - World Wildlife Fund - Conservation and Development in China's Northern Min Mountains, 2001-2007 (Box 57, Folder 361)
  - Yale-China Association, 1986-1989 (Box 58, Folder 362)
  - Yale-China Association - American Studies Summer Institute, Hong Kong, 1995-2002 (Box 58, Folder 363)
  - Yale-China Association - Centennial Campaign, 2000-2005 (Box 58, Folder 364)
  - Yale Divinity School, 1986-1993 (Box 58, Folder 365)
  - Yale Divinity School - H. Richard Niebuhr Lecture Hall, 2000-2005 (Box 74, Folder 461)
  - Yale Law School - China Law Center, 2000-2006 (Box 58, Folder 366)
  - Yale University - Cambodian Genocide Project, 1996-2004 (Box 58, Folder 367-368)
  - Yale University - Collaborative Industrial Ecology in Asia, 2001-2007 (Box 58, Folder 369)
  - Yale University - 50th Anniversary Award, 1986-1989 (Box 59, Folder 370)
  - Yale University - Horace Taft Memorial Fund, 1984-1988 (Box 59, Folder 371)
  - Yale University - Indochina Refugee History, 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 372)
  - Yale University - Jonathan Edwards, 1997-2001 (Box 59, Folder 373)
  - Yale University - Jonathan Edwards (Renewal), 2001-2013 (Box 74, Folder 462)
  - Yale University Library - James Boswell Papers, 1999-2006 (Box 59, Folder 374)
  - Yale University Press - Culture and Civilization of China, 1993-2006 (Box 59, Folder 375-376)
  - Yenching Graduate Institute - Library Reading Room and "Biographical Sketches of Outstanding Yenching People"", 1997-2003 (Box 59, Folder 377)
  - Yenching Graduate Institute - Zhao Zichen, 2000-2004 (Box 60, Folder 378)
  - YWCA National Board - Fund for the Future, 1983-1986 (Box 60, Folder 379)
- Luce Fund for Asian Studies, 1975-2013; 2
  The Luce Fund for Asian Studies awarded grants to foster the study of Asia in American liberal arts colleges. This series contains grant files from the program's inception in 1999 through its final grant competition in 2002. Also included are a series of grants that predate the official establishment of the Luce Fund for Asian Studies which show the Foundation's early support for broadening Asian studies in American universities.
  - 2002 Grants, 2002-2013; 1
    - Bowdoin College - Asian Diasporic Studies, 2002-2012 (Box 74, Folder 463)
    - Claremont McKenna College - East Asian History (Korea), 2002-2010 (Box 74, Folder 464)
    - Hampshire College - History of Global Migrations (Asia), 2002-2012 (Box 74, Folder 465)
    - University of the South Sewanee - Language and Literature (China), 2002-2011 (Box 74, Folder 466)
    - Vassar College - Political Economy (East Asia), 2002-2010 (Box 75, Folder 467)
    - Wellesley College - Comparative Work and Family (Korea or Southeast Asia), 2002-2010 (Box 75, Folder 468)
    - Wittenberg University - Language and Cultural Studies (China), 2002-2013 (Box 75, Folder 469)
  - 2001 Grants, 2001-2013; 2
    - Beloit College - Language and Literature (China), 2001-2013 (Box 75, Folder 470)
    - Colgate University - Language and Culture (China), 2001-2008 (Box 75, Folder 471)
    - Gettysburg College - Language and Culture (China), 2001-2009 (Box 75, Folder 472)
    - Kenyon College - Music and Culture (Asia), 2001-2008 (Box 76, Folder 473)
    - Mount Holyoke College - Politics and Political Economy (China), 2001-2008 (Box 76, Folder 474)
    - St. Olaf College - Visual Culture (East Asia), 2001-2013 (Box 76, Folder 475)
    - Southwestern University - Politics (East Asia), 2001-2007 (Box 76, Folder 476)
    - University of Puget Sound - Islamic Societies (Southeast Asia), 2001-2010 (Box 76, Folder 477)
    - Wesleyan University - Political Economy (East Asia), 2001-2010 (Box 76, Folder 478)
    - Willamette University - Language and Culture (China), 2001-2011 (Box 77, Folder 479)
  - 2000 Grants, 2000-2013; 3
    - Carleton College - Language and Literature (China), 2000-2008 (Box 77, Folder 480)
    - Dickinson College - Language and Culture (China), 2000-2006 (Box 77, Folder 481)
    - Hobart and William Smith Colleges - Art History (East Asia), 2000-2006 (Box 77, Folder 482)
    - Lawrence University - Political Economy (East/Southeast Asia), 2000-2010 (Box 77, Folder 483)
    - Lewis and Clark College - Social Science (China), 2000-2010 (Box 77, Folder 484)
    - Middlebury College - International Studies and Political Science (Japan), 2000-2010 (Box 78, Folder 485)
    - Occidental College - Intellectual and Cultural History (Japan/Korea), 2000-2008 (Box 78, Folder 486)
    - Sarah Lawrence College - Human and Cultural Geography (East Asia), 2000-2006 (Box 78, Folder 487)
    - Skidmore College - Anthropology (East Asia), 2000-2008 (Box 78, Folder 488)
    - Williams College - Economics (East Asia), 2000-2013 (Box 78, Folder 489)
  - 1999 Grants, 1999-2013; 4
    - Bard College - Language and Literature (Japan), 1999-2007 (Box 78, Folder 490)
    - Bates College - Art History (Asia), 1999-2009 (Box 78, Folder 491)
    - College of the Holy Cross - Balinese Theater and Music, 1999-2007 (Box 79, Folder 492-493)
    - Colorado College - Art History (Asia), 1999-2007 (Box 79, Folder 494)
    - Eckerd College - Language and Literature (China), 1999-2010 (Box 79, Folder 495)
    - Hamilton College - Anthropology and Sociology (China), 1999-2007 (Box 79, Folder 496)
    - Oberlin College - Anthropology and Sociology (Northeast Asia), 1999-2013 (Box 79, Folder 497)
    - Reed College - Anthropology (China), 1999-2009 (Box 80, Folder 498)
    - Smith College - Anthropology (East Asia), 1999-2005 (Box 80, Folder 499)
    - Union College - Language and Literature (China), 1999-2012 (Box 80, Folder 500)
    - Whitman College - Art History (Asia), 1999-2006 (Box 80, Folder 501)
  - Early Grants, 1975-1987; 5
    - Stanford University - East Asian Communication and Education, 1980-1983 (Box 80, Folder 502-503)
    - Stanford University - China Relations, 1976-1981 (Box 81, Folder 504)
    - Stanford University - International Science and Technology, 1976-1986 (Box 81, Folder 505)
    - Stanford University - United States-Japan Relations, 1976-1981 (Box 81, Folder 506-507)
    - Stanford University - Resume File, undated (Box 81, Folder 508)
      Restricted from research -- contains personnel material.
    - University of California, Berkeley - General Correspondence, 1975-1987 (Box 81, Folder 509)
    - University of California, Berkeley - United States-Chinese Relations: Perspective on 50 Years, 1976-1981 (Box 81, Folder 510)
    - University of California, Berkeley - After Vietnam: The Cambodian Crisis, 1978-1986 (Box 81, Folder 511)
    - University of California, Berkeley - United States and Southeast Asia, 1976-1979 (Box 82, Folder 512)
    - University of California, Berkeley - Resume File, undated (Box 82, Folder 513)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - General Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 82, Folder 514)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Bermuda Conference (Baum), 1978-1979 (Box 82, Folder 515)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - Trends and Prospects: Sino-American Trade, 1976-1982 (Box 82, Folder 516)
    - University of California, Los Angeles - United States and Japan, 1976-1979 (Box 82, Folder 517)
    - University of Chicago - Liberal and Democratic Thought (China), 1981-1986 (Box 82, Folder 518)
    - University of Chicago - General Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box 82, Folder 519)
    - University of Chicago - Seminar, 1976-1981 (Box 82, Folder 520)
    - University of Chicago - Transformation of American-Chinese-Japanese Relations, 1981-1983 (Box 83, Folder 521)
    - University of Chicago - Rejected Proposals, 1979-1981 (Box 83, Folder 522)
    - University of Chicago - Resume File, 1981 (Box 83, Folder 523)
    - University of Chicago - Financial Statements, 1982 (Box 83, Folder 524)
    - University of Michigan - General Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 83, Folder 525)
    - University of Michigan - National Archive in Sino-American Relations, 1976-1983 (Box 83, Folder 526-527)
    - University of Michigan - American Protestant Missionary Activities in Asia, 1977-1983 (Box 83, Folder 528)
    - University of Michigan - American Application of Japanese Worker Models, 1977-1982 (Box 83, Folder 529-530)
    - University of Michigan - United States-Philippine Interactions in Oral Histories, 1976-1984 (Box 84, Folder 531)
    - University of Michigan - Carter Administration China Policy, 1981-1984 (Box 84, Folder 532)
    - University of Michigan - Resume File, undated (Box 84, Folder 533)
    - University of Southern California - General Correspondence, 1975-1983 (Box 84, Folder 534)
    - University of Southern California - East Asian and Western Cultures, 1978-1984 (Box 84, Folder 535-536)
    - University of Southern California - Zen in American Life and Letters, 1981-1984 (Box 84, Folder 537)
    - University of Southern California - Resume File, undated (Box 84, Folder 538)
    - University of Washington - Korean-American Relations, 1945-1950, 1976-1984 (Box 85, Folder 539)
    - University of Washington - General Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 85, Folder 540)